<!-- Created with FOMOD Creation Tool 1.7.0.37 [http://www.nexusmods.com/fallout4/mods/6821] -->
<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://qconsulting.ca/fo3/ModConfig5.0.xsd">
	<moduleName>dmenu</moduleName> 
	<installSteps order="Explicit"> 
		<installStep name="Developer Options"> 
			<optionalFileGroups order="Explicit"> 
				<group name="Build Type" type="SelectExactlyOne">
					<plugins order="Explicit"> 
						<plugin name="Release"> 
							<description>Installs the Release Build: Highly recommended for most users, offering the highest performance.



Maximum Optimization, No Debugging: This build is optimized for the best performance and does not include debugging information.</description>
							<conditionFlags> 
								<flag name="release">On</flag>
							</conditionFlags>
							<files> 
								<file source="Plugin - Release\wheeler.dll" destination="SKSE\Plugins\wheeler.dll"/>
							</files> 
							<typeDescriptor> 
								<type name="Recommended"/>
							</typeDescriptor>
						</plugin> 
						<plugin name="Debug"> 
							<description>Installs the Debug Build: Ideal for development and testing.



No Optimization, Maximum Debugging: This build provides extensive debug information to assist in diagnosing issues.

Crash Reporting: If the game crashes due to this SKSE plugin, please provide the details for troubleshooting.


Note: While I will review any reports, I cannot guarantee a fix for every bug or crash.</description> 
							<conditionFlags> 
								<flag name="debug">On</flag>
							</conditionFlags>
							<files> 
								<file source="Plugin - Debug\wheeler.dll" destination="SKSE\Plugins\wheeler.dll"/> 
								<file source="Plugin - Debug\wheeler.pdb" destination="SKSE\Plugins\wheeler.pdb"/>
							</files> 
							<typeDescriptor> 
								<type name="Optional"/>
							</typeDescriptor>
						</plugin> 
						<plugin name="RelWithDebInfo"> 
							<description>Installs the RelWithDebInfo Build: Useful for development and testing with performance optimizations.

Optimized Performance with Debug Information: This build includes optimizations along with debug information, making it suitable for troubleshooting performance issues.


Use if the Game Crashes(optional): If the game crashes due to this SKSE Plugin, send the details for investigation.


No Guaranteed Fix: While I'll do my best to help, I can't guarantee a fix for your bug or crash.</description> 
							<conditionFlags> 
								<flag name="RelWithDebInfo">On</flag>
							</conditionFlags>
							<files> 
								<file source="Plugin - RelWithDebInfo\wheeler.dll" destination="SKSE\Plugins\wheeler.dll"/> 
								<file source="Plugin - RelWithDebInfo\wheeler.pdb" destination="SKSE\Plugins\wheeler.pdb"/>
							</files> 
							<typeDescriptor> 
								<type name="Optional"/>
							</typeDescriptor>
						</plugin> 
						<plugin name="MinSizeRel"> 
							<description>Installs the MinSizeRel Build: Ideal for users who need to minimize the size of the build while maintaining reasonable performance.



Minimal Size with Performance: This build is optimized to reduce the executable size, making it suitable for environments with limited storage or distribution constraints.
</description> 
							<conditionFlags> 
								<flag name="MinSizeRel">On</flag>
							</conditionFlags>
							<files> 
								<file source="Plugin - MinSizeRel\wheeler.dll" destination="SKSE\Plugins\wheeler.dll"/>
							</files>
							<typeDescriptor>
								<type name="Optional"/>
							</typeDescriptor>
						</plugin> 
					</plugins>
				</group> 
			</optionalFileGroups>
		</installStep> 
	</installSteps>
</config>

